{
    "exam_name": "Python Assessment",
    "questions": [
        {
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "question": "How to insall package in python?",
            "choices": [
                "npm ",
                "yarn",
                "pip",
                "py"
            ],
            "correct_choice": "pip"
        },
        {
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "question": "What is the python extension ?",
            "choices": [
                ".hs",
                ".p",
                ".py",
                ".pn"
            ],
            "correct_choice": ".py"
        },
        {
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "question": "What is output of 3 != 3 in python?",
            "choices": [
                "0",
                "1",
                "false",
                "true"
            ],
            "correct_choice": "false"
        },
        {
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "question": "What to console the text in python?",
            "choices": [
                "console.log()",
                "println()",
                "print()",
                "cout()"
            ],
            "correct_choice": "print()"
        },
        {
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "question": "What is print 3+3 = ?",
            "choices": [
                "5",
                "6",
                "7"
            ],
            "correct_choice": "6"
        },
        {
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "question": "What is  4**1?",
            "choices": [
                "5",
                "1",
                "0",
                "4"
            ],
            "correct_choice": "4"
        },
        {
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "question": "what is output of 1 === 1?",
            "choices": [
                "1",
                "0",
                "true"
            ],
            "correct_choice": "true"
        },
        {
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "question": "How to make function in python?",
            "choices": [
                "fn",
                "function",
                "def",
                "defination"
            ],
            "correct_choice": "def"
        },
        {
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "question": "if a == a : print(a) else : ",
            "choices": [
                "a",
                "0",
                "9",
                "ab"
            ],
            "correct_choice": "a"
        },
        {
            "type": "Single Choice",
            "question": "what is your name ?",
            "choices": [
                "Vikash",
                "Demo",
                "Memo"
            ],
            "correct_choice": "Vikash"
        }
    ],
    "duration": 1
}